MAYUR SHAH

PMP, Certified Scrum Master (CSM), SAFe 5 Certified Scrum ICP ACC (IC Agile Certified Coach) AWS Certified Solutions Architect

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

+91-9898719270



SUMMARY

Mayur Shah is an experienced Technical Project Manager & Agile coach with overall 11+ years of experience. He has 5+ years of experience in to Project Management and 6.5 Years of experience as a PHP Developer. He has excellent combination of technical, agile project management and leadership skills.

EXPERIENCE

PROGRAM AND PROJECT MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

ACCENTURE INDIA, AHMEDABAD - (JAN 2022-PRESENT)

Working on SAP Finance project as a Scrum Master / Agile Coach and managing a team of 7 people. Responsibilites includes Sprint planning, execution and faciliating scrum ceremonies. Coaching & mentoring the team.

ASSISTANT PROJECT MANAGER

SIGMA SOLVE LTD., AHMEDABAD - (JUNE 2021-JAN 2022)

Worked on end to end delivery of multiple on shore projects and managed a combined team of 20+ people. Responsibilties included but not limited to project planning, execution, stackholder management, scope management, risk management, client communication, budgeting, report generation etc.

TECHNICAL HEAD

GLASIER INC., AHMEDABAD - (JAN 2019-MAY 2021)

Worked on end to end delivery of multiple projects and managed a combined team of 30+ people. Responsiblities included but not limited to project planning, execution, stackholder management, scope management, client communication, budgeting, report generation etc. and helping the team in technical challenges.

SR. PHP DEVELOPER

WEBEE TECHNOLOGIES, AHMEDABAD - (JAN 2018-DEC 2018)

Worked as a technical lead and managed a team of around 10 people. Worked on PHP backend and E-commerce projects. Worked on CorePHP, Codelgnitor, Laravel, WordPress & E-commerce projects. Developed Rest APIs and integrated in web applications.

SR. PHP DEVELOPER

UNLIKE ANYTHING, AHMEDABAD - (MAR 2015-DEC 2017)

Worked on CorePHP, WordPress, E-commerce & Codelgnitor projects. Integrated REST APIs.

WEB DEVELOPER

NECLUES SOFTWARE, AHMEDABAD - (JUN 2012-MAR 2015)

Worked on CorePHP, WordPress, E-commerce & web development projects.

EDUCATION

BECHELOR OF ENGINEERING (INFO. TECHNOLOGY) - (2011)

BHAVNGAR UNIVERSITY - Bhavnagar, Gujarat, India

H.S.C. - (2004)

GUJARAT HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD - Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India

CERTIFICATIONS

PROJECT MANAGEMENT PROFESSIONAL (PMP), CERTIFICATE ID 3638257 ICAGILE CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL IN AGILE COACHING - AUG. 2023 LINK CERTIFIED SAFE® 5 SCRUM MASTER - NOV. 2022 LINK CERTIFIED SCRUM MASTER® FROM SCRUM ALLIANCE - OCT. 2021 LINK AWS CERTIFIED SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT - DEC. 2022 LINK

SKILLS

- Leadership
- **Conflict Resolution**
- Resolving impediments
- Estimation
- Planning
- Reporting
- Budgeting
- Team management
- Coaching & mentoring the team
- Software development life cycle
- Agile project management
- Scrum
- SAFe Agile
- **AWS**
- PHP programming language
- Rest API, API Integration
- MySQL
- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- WordPress

TOOLS

- JIRA
- MICROSOFT AZURE DEVOPS (ADO)
- ZOHO
- **ASANA**
- TRELLO